<resources>
    <string name="app_name">好生活好房</string>
    <string name="login">登陆</string>
    <string name="home_tab_home">首页</string>
    <string name="home_tab_look_house">看房</string>
    <string name="home_tab_message">消息</string>
    <string name="home_tab_mine">我的</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="error_get_verify_code">验证码获取失败，请重试</string>

    <string name="loaded_failed">网络数据加载失败</string>
    <string name="retry">请重试</string>
    <string name="share_error">分享失败</string>

    <string name="text_refund_info"><Data><![CDATA[请上传<font color="#00AAC6"><b>pos支付小票、优惠凭证等&#062;&#062;</b></font>，信息越详细，越易于退款审核。建议上传jpg、png图片，大小1M以内。]]></Data></string>
    <string name="register_agreement_info_up">北京好生活科技有限公司用户，请认真阅读本《用户协议》（以下简称“协议”），确保您充分理解本协议中各条款。请您审慎阅读并选择接受或不接受本协议。除非您接受本协议所有条款，否则您无权注册、登录或使用本协议所涉服务。您的注册、登录、使用等行为将视为对本协议的接受，并同意接受本协议各项条款的约束。</string>

    <string name="register_agreement_info_down">本协议约定好生活科技与用户之间关于“好生活”软件服务（以下简称“服务”）的权利义务。“用户”是指注册、登录、使用本服务的个人。本协议可由好生活科技随时更新，更新后的协议条款一旦公布即代替原来的协议条款，恕不再另行通知，用户可在本网站查阅最新版协议条款。在陌陌科技修改协议条款后，如果用户不接受修改后的条款，请立即停止使用好生活科技提供的服务，用户继续使用好生活科技提供的服务将被视为接受修改后的协议。</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>


    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="invite_rlue">1.可直接让用户通过扫描二维码实现邀请。\n2.点击邀请好友后，复制邀请码发送给好友，好友在注册时填写邀请码，亦可在将二维码分享给对方，即可在对方注册成功后获得100积分奖励。
    </string>
    <string name="brokerage_rule">1.应结佣：成交的客户订单，按照结佣套餐的计算出来，达到结佣节点的佣金金额；\n\n
        2.预计结佣：成交的客户订单，按照结佣套餐计算出来该经纪预计结算的总佣金金额； \n\n
        3.待结佣：成交的客户订单，按照结佣套餐的计算出来，未达到结佣节点的佣金金额；\n\n
        4.应扣税费：网络推客成交客户的佣金收入，按照个人所得税计算税费扣除；\n\n
        5.结佣金额=应结佣-应扣税费金额； \n\n
        6.展示数据为10月1日之后认购成交的订单;
    </string>
    <!--知乎的图片选择器的错误提示-->
    <plurals name="error_over_count">
           
        <item quantity="one">你只能选择一个文件</item>
           
        <item quantity="many">你最多只能选择 %1$d 个文件</item>
    </plurals>
</resources>
